forpressrelease.com 2019-05-09

# Privacy Policy - For Press Release - Online Press Release Distribution Service

|   
---  
|  |  |  |  |  |   
---  
  
**Privacy Policy**

For PressRelease.com is a leading press release distribution service provider that is committed to maintaining the privacy policy to protect the personal information of customers, users and other visitors to our website.

We publish and distribute press releases of our clients that include personal information, contained in the media contact information of the release. When your press release is distributed through our system, your contact information will also be disseminated. This Privacy Policy is applicable on all the services offered by For PressRelease.com.

**Sharing of Information**

For PressRelease.com never shares user information with third parties. The only time the contact information is displayed is during the distribution of the press releases through our system.

At the time of registering an account with us, you need to submit your personal details, which we do not share with others at any time. It is however necessary for you to submit correct details and update it when there is any change in your personal detail. 

However, ForPressRelease and its subsidiary companies may update or send promotional emails on some occasions. 

By having registered with us, you will be able to post press releases with your media contact details. This media contact will be visible to all readers who will access your press release on our website.   

| 

Recently Posted Press News on May 9, 2019    
  
---  

|    
---  
  
Recently Visited Press News on May 9, 2019    

|   
---
